We're here today
with Uhm Jung-hwa and Sooyoung.
Jung-hwa is someone
who's known as Korea's Madonna.
When the chefs heard
Jung-hwa would be joining us,
they said, "Our star is really coming?"
WE'VE BEEN WAITING
-Really?
-Also,
Ho-young said he had trouble sleeping?
-Really?
-I was in the military in 1996,
when a military-themed show
-called Stage of Friendship was on air.
-Stage of Friendship.
Jung-hwa had visited back then and sang
"Love That Only Heaven Allows."
I successfully finished my service
thanks to that performance.
Really? In 1996?
I was a bit disappointed
because I was expecting "Pupil,"
but you sang a ballad instead.
So it kind of killed the vibe.
You were the original star,
popular among soldiers.
-Yes, the troops' favorite.
-She was so popular.
I performed often at military camps.
There were times when the stage collapsed.
GASP
I was quite popular.
Of course.
We're all too familiar with that.
She's not Korea's Madonna.
Madonna is America's Uhm Jung-hwa.
HOW SWEET♥
PLEASED…
I came to Seoul in 1991,
and a singer named Uhm Jung-hwa
debuted in 1993.
I feel like I kind of know her
like a hometown friend.
Where are you from?
I lived in Jecheon for three years.
-Really?
-Yes, I lived there for three years.
Actually, my older sister
was in the same homeroom class
-as Jung-hwa in middle school.
-Really?
REALLY?!
-That's why…
-No way.
…I have heard
a lot about her from my sister.
She said, "Jung-hwa has to be big."
MOVED
-Uhm Jung-hwa.
I must've somehow felt that.
I always loved seeing you on TV.
-I'm her direct junior.
-You are.
-Whoa.
-All right, Sis.
All right.
FRIENDLY HOMETOWN FRIENDS FROM JECHEON
Jung-hwa now has many younger singers
who came after her.
So as you associate with them,
do you ever feel the generational gap?
-Not really.
-No?
-Is it easy to talk to them?
-Yes.
What's it like in your shoes, Sooyoung?
Well…
She's right. I never feel that gap.
You mean me?
-No, me.
-Oh, you.
Me, ma'am.
At times, I find myself
calling her like a friend.
-She's that chill?
-Then Jung-hwa shouldn't have a problem.
I'd be like, "Girl, that's hilarious!"
That means she's really chill.
We received some intel.
-You did?
-Yes.
We heard you were often seen
eating out with younger colleagues.
When I'm scheduled
to go out and eat with her,
I have to set aside a lot of time.
-I see.
-She goes for rounds two and three.
-It's not just lunch.
These days, Gen Z kids will go home
-when you ask them to come.
-Yes.
They feel a lot of pressure.
-They don't like it.
-Really?
And never ask,
"What do you do when you're free?"
-Really?
-Apparently.
I kept asking them.
You did?
I'd ask, "Are you free tomorrow?"
-We aren't supposed to ask.
-We aren't?
-Apparently so.
-You shouldn't.
No calls.
We recently went to dinner
and that day, Sooyoung said,
"Let's go to a karaoke room!"
Do singers do that too?
I was thrilled that she asked.
JELLY…
-Did a medley of Jung-hwa's songs.
-And Girls' Generation.
-A medley of Girls' Generation songs.
-And ours.
It'd take an hour just to do that.
You're right.
You had fun that day, right?
It was so much fun, Jung-hwa!
HER SOCIAL MODE IS AT FULL THROTTLE
That's so awkward.
Let's do that again sometime.
I'D LOVE TO♥
What about you, Eun-yeong?
You must know many older chefs.
It happens from time to time.
Actually, it happened rather often
when I worked with Chef Lu Chinglai.
-So?
-Do I make people feel like that too?
No, that wasn't what I meant.
I loved it.
I always went
because I was grateful for the invite.
What if you don't want to go?
When I didn't feel like it,
I often said I wasn't feeling well.
That I was under the weather.
-You're never sick.
-You must begin
staging your condition an hour before,
like wiping your sweat.
Start the act from the morning.
"Why am I so feverish today?"
Here's something I do.
I keep on yawning.
YAWN
Like you're saying, "I'm tired."
-Like that day?
-"Jung-hwa…"
Like that day?
-She remembers.
-You remember when she yawned?
She remembers that day.
So we all do that.
SOOYOUNG, YOU MUST'VE BEEN TIRED ^^
Sung-jun and Nam-no,
you're both the Gen MZ.
-Yes.
-What if older chefs did this?
We're kind of different from each other.
Yes, Nam-no shows up often.
-I…
-He joins us.
-I show up to these gatherings.
-He does.
Even when I'm sick to death.
Because you love to eat.
-Yes, and that's a good thing.
-Wait.
Sung-jun never says no.
He shoots right home without answering.
RUNS WITHOUT A RESPONSE
I don't pick up my phone.
That's right, he doesn't.
That's why he's Gen MZ.
I can only add it to my schedule
if you give me a week's notice.
-A week?
-A week before?
I can't show up
to these spontaneous gatherings.
Jong-won has something
he wants to share with Jung-hwa
to help her communicate with Gen MZ.
You work with many of them, right?
Yes, my entire staff is Gen MZ,
so it's important
that I understand their language.
These days, the "ya" meme is on the rise.
YA?
-The first one is yareu.
-Yareu.
That's ancient.
-It's been a while.
It's already ancient?
It's outdated.
YAREU: LIKE "WOOHOO" OR "SLAY"
It's a bit old.
-There's another one, city name and yaho.
-Yaho.
-That too.
THAT'S OLD TOO…
Not like what you say it
on top of a mountain? "Yaho"?
-It's not what you say when hiking.
-No?
It's not this yaho.
KNOWS MORE THAN YOU THINK
I heard it just this morning.
-You did?
-I went to get my makeup done
and the younger staff members there
told me about it.
I said, "Isn't it 'yaho'?"
-You went through this.
-Yes.
It's the hikers' "yaho."
-At the top of Buramsan Mountain.
-But it wasn't that.
-Buramsan Mountain?
-Instead of that,
you still say the same thing
with a nasal voice.
NASAL VOICE GALORE
JUST LIKE THIS
MOVED
It's something Japanese gyaru girls said,
and it recently came back.
"Geoje, yaho."
You just do it without any context?
-It's a greeting. When you meet someone.
-A greeting?
-That's the end of the meme.
-Let's try it…
-…with our hometowns.
-Jinjeop-eup.
-Jinjeop-eup, go first.
Jinjeop-eup, yaho.
TRENDY
-Great job.
-He's good.
Jecheon, yaho.
IMMEDIATELY USES WHAT THEY LEARNED
Let's go with the meme from our day.
It's great to see you.
Hi, hi.
OF COURSE WE KNOW THAT
-Hey!
-Homegirl!
SPRINGS TO HER FEET
UP AND DOWN
-That's it.
-I've seen it in a drama.
HAVE FUN LIKE WE'VE GONE BACK IN TIME!
We should be using that.
FEELS RIGHT AT HOME
The biggest reason why Jung-hwa thinks
she gets along with younger colleagues
is because of her
extraordinary ability to empathize.
She always hears out people's troubles
with all her heart.
I'm just a good listener.
I think that's important.
-I see.
-And after they're done,
you invite them to a team dinner.
-We can talk as we eat.
-As they eat.
IT'S FUN FOR EVERYONE, RIGHT?
She's like Oh Eun-young, the psychiatrist,
to her colleagues.
I'M PARK EUN-YEONG
So we prepared something.
Our chefs were in need of advice,
so they asked anonymously.
That sounds like a lot of fun.
-She's very empathetic.
-Can I really empathize with you?
Please hear them out,
empathize with them, and provide advice.
Here's the first story.
"I feel more at home
on the show these days,
so at times, people show a great response
-to something random I say."
-Great response?
"Does this mean I can be funny too?"
Someone who isn't funny must've said that.
-"I felt confident and began to chime in…"
-I think I know.
"…but I become really down
when people don't laugh."
I get it. This is so true.
-Is it Jong-won?
-"Especially so
when I look at Jung-hwan
after saying something."
"Because I can tell exactly
that what I said wasn't funny."
WHO SAID THIS, WHO?
He's a cynic, so he has
a high standard for jokes.
But he'd laugh at most things.
"After that, I feel so small."
"What am I supposed to do?"
I guess he's a bit timid.
When you begin to feel small,
it can last a long time.
So don't look at Jung-hwan.
Instead, keep chiming in.
-One of them will be funny.
-Don't look?
-Make jokes for yourself.
-For himself.
But he scolds me.
-Yeah?
-He tells me to stop.
Ignore that too.
Yes, you should ignore it.
-Was it Jong-won?
-It was you?
-Was it you?
Oh, gosh.
A MAN WHO WANTS TO BE FUNNY
A MAN WHO JUST WON'T LAUGH
I feel bad for my dear Chef Jong-won.
Even during the last shoot,
he said, "Enough is enough."
-"Enough is enough."
-I said that?
I'll use tenderloin
to let you sound tender.
WILL JUNG-HWAN LAUGH AT THIS?
He threw in a joke.
INDIFFERENT…
Excuse me. You're trying too hard.
I think this is the first time
I'm speaking today.
That was why he wasn't talking.
-He was sitting like this.
-Right.
DISHEARTENED
A host should laugh at every joke.
-Of course. He's a host, not an athlete.
-Right?
I'll just keep smiling.
It looks great on you.
Laugh more often.
It wasn't funny,
so how was I supposed to laugh?
It's not like it's a crime.
It's worse to force out laughter…
I also don't find everything funny!
IN SHREDS
-Okay?
-It wasn't funny.
-Is this a crime?
-Just laugh a bit more.
Fine. I'll keep smiling.
Keep smiling
until he builds up enough tolerance.
-There's one last story.
-Another one?
"I love to eat almost too much,
so I know when I should stop,
but it's hard to do so."
"When I see food before me,
my throat tickles."
IT EVEN TICKLES?
"When I eat eggs in the green room
to lose weight, my appetite kicks in."
-His appetite kicks in?
-"So I end up eating ramyeon,
toast, and two lunch boxes."
-It's probably Jung or Yoon.
-Yes.
What should he do?
-He should eat.
-And overcome it? No?
That's what makes him happy.
It would be great to start with eggs,
but I don't want you to lose
that endearing quality,
Mr. Nam-no.
It might not be me.
THE MAN BEHIND THE STORY
SOMEHOW GOT EXPOSED
-He said this too.
-What?
"I even won against a GLP-1 drug."
-That's incredible.
-He's something.
I've been trying to cut down on dinner,
and someone told me to try eating eggs.
That's the trend.
But I ended up eating 12 eggs in total.
Once I begin, I can't stop.
Were you at a chicken coop?
Some may feel motivated by you
and want to stay in shape like you,
but the thing is, it may not happen.
What would you say to those people?
-It's so hard.
-It is?
You have to try, though reluctantly.
It's all about what you eat.
It's not the advice itself.
It's the way she talks to you.
She looks into your eyes
with her inner brows raised like this.
-So it's already comforting.
-You're right.
-Really?
-It feels like it's resolved. That's it.
She might ask you
to stay for a group dinner.
Really?
I'd love to go.
Can you karaoke for three hours?
-I love going to a karaoke room!
-He'll stay for rounds two and three.
STAGING HER ACT
STAGING HERS TOO
I'm sure the secret
behind how she stays in shape…
-Let's open her fridge.
-…is all in her fridge.
I heard the secret
to her youthful look is inside.
Keep a close eye on it.
When she gets health checkups,
her body age comes out
as someone in her 20s or 30s.
-Yes.
-Right?
I'll be six years old soon.
Her time flows backwards.
HAS NO RESPONSE…
Sorry. I just throw things out there.
-Let's see what she has.
-I want to see it.
Let's take a look at Jung-hwa's fridge.
-What's the secret to her youthfulness?
-What is it?
We present Jung-hwa's fridge!
-Here we go.
-My gosh.
WHOA
We present Jung-hwa's fridge!
HER FRIDGE IS TOTALLY YAREU
And you live alone.
-You have a lot of stuff. I knew it.
-She does.
That's a lot.
Were you surprised, Sooyoung?
-I was.
-You didn't think she'd have this much?
Do you not find grocery shopping tedious?
Whenever I have time, I like to go
to the farmers' market.
-Farmers' market?
-Yes.
-With actual farmers?
-Yes, you've probably heard of Marche.
-Yes, Marche.
It's put together
to support small farmers…
What now?
-Wait.
-What now?
-Don't be mad. Hear him out.
-He said something.
-Listen to what he says.
-What now?
I was commenting.
I wasn't trying to be funny.
-I wanted to hear you out.
-Tell us.
It's called Marche, something that
opens three to four times a month.
Farmers gather to let consumers come
to buy produce directly from them.
-So it's not open every day?
-No.
And they also have vegetables
and fruits with small flaws.
With lower commercial value.
-There's a market that sells those too.
-But it's good.
I like to get my produce from such places,
so it's cheaper, but still delicious.
-And you have your haul in here? Okay.
-Yes.
-Let's take a look.
-From the top.
The top shelf.
These are… Oh, eggs.
-They're bluish.
-Those are blue-shelled eggs.
-And they're tiny.
-That's cool.
From Jecheon, my friend…
-From our Jecheon.
-Yes, from Jecheon?
Yes, my friend runs a restaurant,
so I get those eggs
from the chicken farm that does business
with my friend.
WOW
There are some sauces down here.
I probably have lots of sauces.
Yes, you have them here and here.
-Those are all low-sugar sauces.
-They are.
Yes, these are all labeled "low-sugar."
Low-sugar oyster sauce.
This is low-sugar too.
A sponge cake, castella.
I've kept a low-carb, high-fat diet
for a long time.
Ever since I started,
my hormone balance
and the quality of sleep
improved drastically.
After your low-carb, high-fat diet?
She chugs bottles of every kind of spirit,
so how is her body age in her thirties?
-That doesn't have an impact.
-It doesn't.
I get that you have a low-carb diet,
but this is low-sugar.
I've been doing low-carb, low-sugar.
-Low-carb, low-sugar.
-Do you not eat rice?
-I do.
It's not that
I've cut out carbs altogether.
-I keep it at 30%.
-It's low-carb. About 30%?
-Yes, you don't cut it out.
-Right.
What's this? Noodles?
It's like tofu noodles.
-Zero sugar.
-Yes.
When I'm on a diet,
I always crave noodles.
-So substitutes.
-Yes, substitutes.
I substitute everything.
The toughest craving is jjajangmyeon.
Gosh, jjajangmyeon.
-It's so good.
-Yes, it's so good.
IT IS GOOD
-Do you like strong-tasting food?
-Yes.
I do, but I hold myself back.
-She holds back.
-And she likes noodles.
At times, when I get too hungry,
I watch mukbang.
LIVING VICARIOUSLY THROUGH MUKBANGS
You can let loose once a month, right?
Yes, so I eat it from time to time.
After I eat something like that,
I stay on an empty stomach
for 18 to 20 hours.
You fast?
People who try to keep in shape
usually fast.
THE BEST AT SELF-DISCIPLINE
I see some side dishes back here.
-Yes.
-Side dishes.
I made that one.
A SIDE DISH SHE MADE?
-You made it?
-What is it? Anchovies?
-Stir-fried anchovies.
-With nuts.
I had already added lots of allulose,
so I regret adding
another dash at the end.
She made it, so we should all try some.
-You're trying it?
-We will.
-I'm so nervous.
-It's really good.
-It is? It is, right?
-Yes.
It seems like she can cook.
-Whoa.
-Hey.
It's just sweet enough.
I want some rice.
-Just have a taste.
-You aren't eating a whole meal. Wait.
OBEDIENT…
Is there anything else
you want to show off?
My mom's salt-pickled cucumbers.
-I love that.
-That sounds good.
-It's perfect for summer.
-A summer delicacy.
-It's great with rice.
-I should go again.
-Again?
-I want to try it.
He's trying that too?
IT ALREADY LOOKS DELICIOUS
-Mmm.
-It's not too salty.
-It's so good.
-It's good.
-Isn't it seasoned perfectly?
Whoa. This is to die for.
It tastes like mom's cooking.
It's really good.
She'll be thrilled to see this.
She loves this show.
Mom, are you watching this?
Ma'am, this is so good.
-We'll call her Madam Pickles now.
-Yes.
-Madam Pickles.
You have that DNA from your mother.
And down here. Vegetables.
She has lots.
I see cucumbers and cabbage in here.
You must like carrots.
I love carrots so much.
So when I'm at a supermarket
or when I shop for produce online,
I buy them out of habit,
even when I have some.
-Not many like these. Some pick them out.
-Right?
I love the sweetness that comes
when carrots are cooked.
You're right.
Are these cucumbers? Yellow cucumbers?
-I've never seen them.
-Zucchinis.
-That's a zucchini.
-Zucchini?
It's excellent for summer pasta.
Whoa.
-So it's a thing?
-What's it like?
Don't you know, Chef Poong?
I'm not a chef, so I don't really know.
I don't think that's a popular ingredient.
-We've never seen it on the show.
-Really?
Where did you get these?
-At the farmers' market.
-The farmers' market.
-It's not easy to find them.
-So you got these there?
What's this?
-Those are really pretty.
-What's this? Broccoli?
-Romanesco broccoli?
-Yes.
-A mix of cauliflower and broccoli.
-And broccoli.
It's similar,
but that tastes much more buttery.
-Lettuce.
No, that isn't lettuce.
-It's red shiso.
-Red lettuce?
-Shiso?
-It's red shiso?
-Shiso.
-Shiso. I thought it was lettuce.
I thought it was lettuce, but it's not.
I really love those.
I eat them raw as a veggie wrap,
and I add them to water too, right there.
-This one?
-Whoa.
-What's this?
-I see the red shiso here.
-All of my favorites are in it.
-What's in here?
Herbs, mint,
basil, red shiso, cucumber,
and lemon.
REFRESHING VEGGIES, MUSTER
-It's refreshing when you drink it.
-It is.
What's your favorite among these?
Supersweet corn.
-Supersweet corn?
-Supersweet corn.
I can't hold back from eating those.
-It's tough to hold back from.
-They're crunchy.
I see some fruits,
like watermelon, tomatoes, and apples.
Look how vibrant the color is.
-That's the one I got…
-It's bright red.
-What is that?
-…from the ugly produce market.
It's from the ugly produce market?
-Less conventionally valuable.
-With little flaws.
But look at these.
They come in different sizes too.
They're not that ugly.
It's bright red.
All of her vegetables look great.
She tries very hard to keep in shape,
but she still keeps
these bottles next to everything.
Is this vodka? What's this?
It's probably some traditional liquor.
-Traditional liquor?
-It was a present.
-What's this? It's halfway gone.
-White wine.
I had leftover wine, so I kept it
for cooking.
-For cooking?
-Yes.
Most people say that.
I usually pop a new bottle when I drink.
You usually keep in shape,
but you drink a little, right?
Yes, to keep my feelings in shape.
PRODUCE FOR HER BODY,
DRINKS FOR HER FEELINGS
I have to keep
my feelings in shape every day.
CAN BE HARMFUL WHEN OVERDONE
He's serious about that.
She's the master of self-discipline,
who takes care of her body and feelings.
That's all for Jung-hwa's fridge!
-You have a lot of stuff.
-I do, right?
Currently, six chefs remain.
-That's why…
-He's right.
…one of the rounds
will be played as teams.
-Wow.
-A team round.
A two-on-two round.
For this team round,
the two chefs
aren't going to cook at once.
-It'll be a tag team round.
-A tag team round.
Taking turns.
-That sounds like so much fun. My gosh.
-It does.
THAT'S TOTALLY YAREU
-So two chefs will cook in relay.
-A tag team round.
It's our first two-on-two tag team round.
I'm so excited for this.
There are people who always play in teams.
-Some chefs are good at this.
-Like Ho-young and Sam.
-Why don't you give it a go?
-Actually,
we've always cooked individually,
-but it felt like a team round.
-Right.
SAM AND HO-YOUNG'S ONE-TEAM SPIRIT
I've always played as a team,
-so we probably have good teamwork.
-All right.
All right, then.
Does anybody want
to go against Sam and Ho-young?
I'll go.
-Who should I take?
-With whom?
-You need a partner.
-You need someone.
-I'll take…
-Someone has to want to join.
…someone I deem my younger sister.
I thought it'd be nice to cook
with Moon-jung, Chef Moon-jung today.
So she'll do the heavy lifting.
What do you think, Moon-jung?
When my skills meet Poong's creativity,
-it'll be a great collaboration.
-That sounds great.
No matter what the order is,
Sam and Ho-young
-will go against Poong and Moon-jung.
-We'll fight.
That automatically leaves
Jong-won and Yong-wook.
You'll have to face each other
no matter what the order is.
Now, let us show you
the orders Jung-hwa brought.
-The orders.
-What is it?
-Okay, Land.
-Okay, Land?
-What is it?
We spent a long time on a cruise ship
while filming Okay! Madam 2.
So at times, we missed the food
we could have back on land.
When you're on a ship,
you can be anywhere when you wake up.
So I want you to get off
wherever you would like
and make me something delicious.
The country doesn't matter.
-No.
-It's not designated.
You're free to choose
whichever country you wish to go to.
-We can go to China.
-But a dish from the land.
-A dish from the land.
-China.
The next one. What's the next order?
What's Jung-hwa looking to eat?
-Junky Low-Carb, Low-Sugar.
-Junky Low-Carb, Low-Sugar
There are times
when I crave that junk food flavor,
and I sometimes fall asleep
while watching mukbang,
which makes my mouth water so much.
Something that has
minimal carbs and sugar,
yet tastes junky, and deadass deli…
OOPS…
-Deadass delicious.
-Junky yet very delicious.
Something that good.
So low-carb, low-sugar, deadass delicious.
Feel free to fixate on "junky" flavor.
-Something junky? Okay.
-Yes.
Director Yong-wook,
you're still considered a rookie here.
He hasn't been here for long.
You'll get the first pick.
-I'm so excited.
-The food I make
is something you'd say it's of the land,
so I'll go with Okay, Land.
Okay, Land.
JONG-WON AUTOMATICALLY JOINS THE ROUND
-Wait a second.
-Everything's decided.
Then the team round will be
Junky Low-Carb, Low-Sugar.
Can that team make junk food…
I'm that junky guy.
Is that okay, Sam?
-It sounds fun.
-Really?
-Good.
-Then it's decided.
Now, let us begin with the first round,
the individual match.
Yong-wook and Jong-won's
15-minute cook-off is coming right up!
The first round of cook-off
with Jung-hwa's ingredients.
Now on the Road to Son,
Director Yoo Yong-wook,
versus the new gatekeeper,
Chef Son Jong-won.
EXCITED
You've already defeated Poong.
YOO YONG-WOOK DEFEATED POONG
IN THE DEBUT ROUND
His next target is Jong-won.
NEXT UP, THE CURRENT SOLE 1ST PLACE
-Yong-wook said something like this.
-What?
"I won the previous cook-off
thanks to Chef Jong-won."
What do you mean?
WHAT'S GOING ON BETWEEN YOU TWO?
While I was literally shuddering
in the green room,
someone suddenly came and patted my back.
And it felt like,
"It's all right. You got this."
I turned my head and saw my older bro
tapping my shoulder lightly.
He's older?
-I was born in 1986.
-We're 2 years apart.
Two years?
His help played a big role.
Jong-won's now like a cult leader.
He tapped Yong-wook's back,
and he could suddenly see again.
But I'm dead serious.
My palpitating heart
suddenly calmed down instantly.
PREACH IT
I was parched,
and I had to get some water,
so I was telling him to move.
To move him?
"Move it! I'm thirsty!"
"Don't stand there."
I don't like violence,
so I just tapped him gently.
-So that was it.
-Like, "Excuse me."
-"Excuse me"?
-He went with it.
-He's a funny guy.
You've been funny lately.
MANAGED TO MAKE THE TOUGH JUNG-HWAN LAUGH
You're funny. Jong-won's funny.
AMAZED
-He's now funny too.
-He needs someone to get it out of him.
EXCUSE ME, COMEDIANS
-They have something in common.
-They do?
-Yes.
They have both
been in charge
of the Presidential state dinner.
-Really?
-Is that so?
Do you remember that day, Jong-won?
I remember President Macron telling me
that our team had great teamwork,
and he said, "Bravo."
He even said, "Bravo, Chef."
FULLY CHARGED WITH EXCITEMENT
DIRECTOR YONG-WOOK'S INGREDIENTS:
CARROT, CABBAGE, ZUCCHINI, RED ONION
MINI BELL PEPPER, CUCUMBER, TOMATO,
SALSA VERDE, RED SHISO, AND MORE
Director Yong-wook, what are you making?
My dish is called
Brazil, Yareu.
-Brazil, Yareu.
-It sounds somewhat passionate.
-It does.
When I imagined a cruise docked at a port,
it reminded me of her explosive energy.
I wondered which country has
that kind of energy
-and decided to dock in Brazil.
-Brazil's great.
Now, there's a deep-fried Brazilian dish
called pastel.
Yes, pastel.
It's made with
a hearty amount of filling
inside a wrapper, then deep-fried.
So I'll make that.
You said you love supersweet corn,
so I'll add
a bit of a South American touch
-by grilling them over fire.
-Sounds great.
I'll also make a cocktail
called Caipirinha.
-Caipirinha.
-Yes.
It's a Brazilian cocktail made with lime.
You don't have the actual liquor,
but I can make it taste similar,
so I'll use the liquor you had
and make you a nice meal
alongside a Caipirinha.
ALMOST TOO MUCH YAREU
CHEF JONG-WON'S INGREDIENTS:
ZUCCHINI, MINI WATERMELON, RED ONION
SUPERSWEET CORN, ROMANESCO BROCCOLI,
RED SHISO, TOMATO PASTE, AND MORE
Jong-won is up next. What are you making?
I want to take Jung-hwa
-on a world tour.
-A world tour?
Where are you starting?
The name of my dish is
South America, Europe, Korea,
Yaho.
THE CRUISE PASSENGER LOOKS PLEASED
AS ALWAYS, TRIED TOO HARD…
CLAPPING…
CHEF & MY FRIDGE ALSO HAS WONI,
SON JONG-WONI
-Yaho. My gosh.
-Smile. Smile a little.
-That was almost too funny.
-Wasn't it?
So just now,
my toes even curled. Can't you see?
-Like this?
-Yes, they curled.
-I know what that is.
-It was too funny.
If you saw him at his restaurant,
you'd never think he'd be like this.
-My gosh.
-He only does it for the show.
-Really.
-For laughs.
So what are you making?
I believe vegetable dishes
are truly the food of the land,
because they can only grow on land.
-So today, I will…
-What's he doing?
LEAVING THE KITCHEN WITH A VEGGIE BASKET
That's so pretty.
My gosh. What is that?
BRINGS THE VEGGIES TO JUNG-HWA!
I prepared three different dishes today.
And they are…
EMERGENCY
It's a fine dining experience.
First off,
I'll use watermelon and red shiso
-to make South America's ceviche.
-It already sounds good.
Next, I'll use the golden zucchini
and make zucchini steak.
Lastly, I'll use supersweet corn and make
-corn beomuri, steamed rice cake.
-Corn beomuri?
That way, you'll experience
that warm welcome back home.
There's a story to it.
-Would you like to take a picture?
-Sure.
They look different like that,
unlike how they were in the fridge.
A fine dining experience.
CLICK
#FINE_DINING_YAREU
-Shall we go on this cruise trip?
-Sure thing.
Where should the ship dock?
Let us begin the cook-off
titled Okay, Land for Jung-hwa.
The global unorthodox chef
approved by the Brazilian president,
-Samba Yoo.
-Samba?
Samba Yoo.
The French president
left him a comment, "Bravo, Chef."
Bonjour Son, Chef Son Jong-won
is up for the challenge.
To which chef will Jung-hwa say okay to?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Let's go!
THE CRUISE TAKES OFF
You're making the wrapper now?
I'm looking forward
to the Brazilian dishes.
-Is that starch?
-Right? What's that? Starch?
-It's starch and flour.
-Flour and starch.
-Olive oil?
-Yes, I'll deep-fry this later.
Are you making the pastel?
-You're right.
-Salt.
That's a unique way of making dough.
-Director Yong-wook is at it.
-He could've just used
the immersion blender.
-It's okay. It only takes two minutes.
-Really?
Then I'll let it rest.
We usually stick to the immersion blender.
But he doesn't trust it yet.
I haven't gotten used to it.
I don't know what it's like.
-So he's using his hands.
-He'd rather do it himself.
-But it takes more time.
-It seems so.
I have enough time.
-Are those breadcrumbs? Rice.
-What's that?
-Rice?
-Rice.
That's how it turned out?
-Nice job.
-What's that?
-Rice powder? That's how you do it?
-He made it himself.
I'm using rice to make beomuri.
I'll use her supersweet corn
that a farmer worked very hard on.
-The supersweet corn.
-Corn.
GRINDING
He's blending the corn.
-That must be good as is.
-I agree.
This means Chef Jong-won
has saved quite a lot of time.
The dumpling wrapper.
Not only must the wrapper turn out nicely,
but once he fries it,
it'll take a while
for the filling to cook.
-I see.
-Done.
-All right.
-He's resting it.
You're going to rest it too?
Five minutes.
-Five minutes?
-You'll let it rest for five minutes?
I'll let him know at eight minutes.
The rice? What's he doing
with the rice powder? Baekseolgi?
Beomuri.
MAKING BEOMURI
-It's similar to seolgi.
-You'll steam it?
The dough is usually made with water,
but I'll use corn juice
to add a nice color.
He's using lots of corn.
How pretty.
MIX WELL, POUR INTO A STEAMER
-Is that…
-He's spreading it even.
Isn't it too thin for seolgi?
To let it cook quickly.
-It's beomuri.
-I'm so excited.
Cabbage.
MAKING THE DUMPLING FILLING
He's julienning the cabbage.
2. THINLY SLICE THE CABBAGE
Yong-wook is using
both carrots and zucchinis.
Jung-hwa especially
loves carrots very much.
She juices it every morning.
Is he grilling the cabbage?
On a gridiron?
-This is his thing.
-Cabbage.
-Zucchini.
-Grilling is his thing.
All those ingredients
are something that I love, so…
-You must be excited.
-Yes.
Next, hanging tender.
-Good.
-He's grilling meat,
-…although he didn't bring his grill.
-Hanging tender.
He's using four… no, three burners
to grill everything.
I'm making the first vegetable dish,
vegetarian dish of the show.
-It's vegetarian?
-Vegetarian?
-It's vegetarian.
-Only vegetables?
He grabs the zucchinis.
That's what it looks like in the middle.
TAPPING
What's he doing?
-He's making cuts.
-He's making cuts?
-But why?
-To make them pretty.
-It's to let them cook well.
-To let them cook well.
INTO A HEATED PAN
You're using no meat, Jong-won?
-Sorry? No meat.
-No meat?
-No meat.
-How fun.
FUN POINTS, 5
-This is fun.
-He grabbed that new veggie.
Romanesco broccoli.
It's a type of cauliflower.
-It looks like broccoli.
-Let me cut some tiny pieces.
It's all about delicate prepping.
2. BLANCH ROMANESCO BROCCOLI
IN SALTED WATER, THEN COOL
NEXT UP, RED SHISO AND MINT!
CHOPPING WITH GOOD VIBES
That's so cool.
That's really cool.
RED ONION
PEPPER
DICE!
It's red shiso.
OLIVE OIL, LIME JUICE
CEVICHE SAUCE IS DONE
Ten minutes.
You have ten minutes!
-Ten minutes?
-Ten minutes.
-What's he doing? A cucumber?
-Cucumber.
Cucumber?
Cucumber. For the sauce.
-For the sauce.
-The sauce.
Did I bite off more than I could chew?
STARTING TO GET SCARED…
It must be tough to follow through.
Ten minutes.
He's grating tomatoes too.
-He's making salsa.
-Salsa.
-What's that? Sun-dried tomato?
-Sun-dried tomato.
Sun-dried tomato.
Flip the meat once.
-The meat.
-It's fine.
It's still a while.
Director Yong-wook surely does know
a lot about grilling food.
-He can grill anything.
-It's hot.
The veggies are a bit too big
to be used as the filling.
I'm going to ch-ch-chop everything.
STILL NOT AN EXPERT AT ANSWERING…
Do-do-don't talk to him.
This is insane. I can hear stuff today.
Last time, I couldn't hear anything.
-This is bad.
-He can hear us today.
You have to flip the meat!
-The wrapper.
-It's fine.
-It's still fine.
-It is?
You said you'd rest the dough
only for five minutes!
-No.
-Then get to it already.
-No? Do you need more time?
-I'll get to it.
Supersweet corn.
If you're busy,
you don't have to answer us.
-But I can hear you.
-You have to answer.
Only then will you be on TV!
Only your answers will make it on air!
Poong, that's a warning.
Yes, you were too loud.
This is bad.
-It's so hectic.
-Cooking wine.
4. MIX CORN WITH VARIOUS CONDIMENTS
He's using lots of corn.
CHECKING ON THE ZUCCHINI
COOKED TO GOLDEN BROWN
The golden zucchini looks so good.
He'll now start to arroser, or baste.
ARROSER, BASTING:
COOKING BY POURING BUTTER OR OIL
That looks good.
How sexy.
That's so sexy.
People are cheering for him.
My gosh!
-He's so cool!
-My gosh!
THIS ZUCCHINI IS TOTALLY…
-Yareu!
Yareu!
-Jong-won, yaho.
WE'LL OVERUSE THIS MEME
AND PULL THE SHUTTERS DOWN
-We can't use that anymore.
-Yareu!
ZUCCHINI INTO THE OVEN!
He's capturing the ladies' hearts.
Jong-won cuts the watermelon.
He's making thin slices.
Watermelon on a slicer?
It's watermelon ceviche.
-Watermelon ceviche?
-That sounds good.
4. TOP WATERMELON WITH GROUND PEPPER,
OLIVE OIL, SALT, AND LIME ZEST
That looks so good.
Eight minutes.
Okay.
I love grilled veggies.
GRABS THE VEGGIES FIRST
-That looks so good.
-Right now…
He has to make a Caipirinha too.
-The dough.
-It takes a while to make one.
-You're halfway through.
-I'm fine.
An onion. A red onion.
CHOPPING
He's good with the knife.
You two are both unorthodox,
yet the knife skills…
-That's nice.
-They're different.
-He's much better.
-He's much better than you.
-You have no time.
-Chop the veggies.
The dough.
-He should make the wrapper.
-The dough?
Can I ask Sung-jun for help?
-I have to help?
-What now?
-Suddenly?
PICKED OUT OF THE BLUE
PRETTY FAR DISTANCE
I can't do that.
That's not how you do it.
It's not even allowed for Poong.
Hurry up and do it.
-The meat is ready.
-Yes, the meat is ready.
He has no time. What will he do?
-He really doesn't have time.
-Make just one.
-Just use a little bit of dough.
-Make just one piece.
-Not too much.
-That's how he's flattening it.
-It's not working.
-This isn't working.
-Is there a rolling pin?
-Use your hands.
-A pin would make it too thick.
-Just let it go through a few times.
-Use your hands for now.
-He tries the machine again.
-It's working.
It's way too small.
This is bad. It's an emergency!
-I want to help him.
-Can you help him a little?
-It's coming apart. Just use this.
-It's falling apart.
I want to roll it for him.
Six minutes left.
It's hard to flatten
when you use lots of oil for the dough.
And he has to deep-fry that too.
-He must be reluctant to use machines.
-I guess.
And you'll wrap the filling in it, right?
-Yes.
-That's right.
And deep-fry it too.
You have to throw it in soon.
Only five minutes left.
Sung-ju, please check the kitchen.
-Five minutes.
-Just deep-fry it over high heat.
Let me go check.
You have five minutes.
It won't take long to deep-fry it.
I only need three minutes.
-You have four minutes and fifty seconds.
-Four minutes.
-Okay.
-Three minutes? You should start now.
Okay.
Well, everything inside is cooked.
-He just has to cook the wrapper.
-If it turns out well, it'll be good.
Can you fit everything in?
Yes, everything is in.
-Is this enough?
-Yes.
-It's okay. You got this.
-I got this.
You got this!
-You got this.
-Is that cheese?
-I think it'll work.
-Be careful.
-Careful.
-Okay.
He'll now deep-fry the dumpling.
It's going in.
-It's going in.
-The heat shouldn't be too high.
Don't let it pop.
GETTING UP
I don't think you should deep-fry it.
Wait, no!
EVERYONE CHIMES IN
SHE GETS UP TOO
-Stick it in oil.
-Fry it.
Wait, the oil isn't hot enough.
It's not hot enough?
The oil is too cold.
-But still, just throw it in.
-Yes, just throw it in.
-You have no time. Go. Use a strainer.
-Put it in first.
GOING IN FOR NOW
-Raise the heat.
-No! It's not hot enough!
BOTH IN DESPAIR
It's way too cold.
-He should use a pan.
-Move it into a pan!
CAN HE DO THIS IN 3 AND A HALF MINUTES?
…COMPLETELY OUT OF IT
Isn't the heat too high for the cabbage?
The cabbage!
I didn't put it in.
WHAT?
-No!
-The cabbage isn't what's important.
CLAPPING AT THE SAME TIME
-The garnish.
-Serve it as the garnish!
It's okay! Don't put it in.
What cabbage? You don't need it.
Garnish. Yes.
It was supposed to be a garnish.
SHUSH
-Okay.
-Put it on the side.
My mixing bowl.
IN GREAT HASTE
But it's burning. The cabbage's burning.
THE "IT'S BURNING" ATTACK
This is so hectic.
If it gets too rowdy,
throw something at him.
AND QUIET POONG DOWN
I forgot to grill the corn.
Oh, my gosh.
CORN RIBS ON THE GRIDIRON
You have three long minutes left.
-Two minutes and fifty seconds.
It seems like Jong-won has the advantage.
DICED RED ONION & PEPPER
TOMATO PASTE, MINCED GARLIC
WHITE WINE, LEMON JUICE
TOMATO SAUCE FOR THE ZUCCHINI
TIME TO CHECK ON THE ZUCCHINI!
5. TOP ZUCCHINI WITH BURRATA
AND SLICED CHEESE, TOAST IN OVEN
Jong-won looks relaxed.
-I'm not particularly relaxed.
-You aren't?
What's this?
I made it so she can enjoy the flavors
from Spain, France, and Italy.
-The flavor of Europe.
-European flavor.
Will Jung-hwa's world tour be a success?
Will it be a success?
-Huh?
-It's a bit unfamiliar.
-It's unfamiliar?
Is it a new land?
-But it's good.
-I'm so curious.
He's now making Caipirinha.
POUNDING THE LIMES
LIQUOR
ALLULOSE
He extracted the juice from the limes.
THE OIL IS MUCH HOTTER THAN BEFORE
It's fine now. Okay.
It's fine. Even better, actually.
-It won't pop.
-Even better.
You still have two minutes.
You can do it!
I can do this!
He's making a Caipirinha.
RED SHISO, SPARKLING WATER
ICE
That looks good.
-It's more fun to watch this side.
-Right? The helter-skelter side is fun.
-He seems lost.
-Yes, and in haste.
There's fun in this raw energy.
BUT I WANTED TO BE FUNNY…
He's like me.
LOL
HE HAS THAT NAM-NO VIBE
-I'm using the barbecue sauce I found.
-Like that?
6. MIX BARBECUE SAUCE,
GRATED CUCUMBER, AND SALSA
-The sauce.
-The sauce!
Does it make you go, "Yareu"?
-Oh, no. Forty seconds.
-Does it make you go, "Yareu"?
Yarrrrreu!
TOTALLY YAREU!
-The sauce is really good!
-Yarrreu!
I can't have only the sauce be good.
Everything else should be too,
but the sauce is good, at least.
WHAT'S JONG-WON UP TO?
FIRST, THE CEVICHE DRESSING
CUTS OFF THE EDGES OF THE WATERMELON
Jong-won begins to plate the food.
DRESSING, FETA, MINT
FINISHING OFF WITH LIME ZEST
NEXT, PULLING OUT ZUCCHINI!
THE MELTED CHEESE LOOKS AMAZING
LAYING OUT TOMATO SAUCE
ZUCCHINI STEAK, GROUND PEPPER
Thirty seconds.
You'd better finish up, Jong-won.
SERVED WITH ROMANESCO BROCCOLI!
What about this one?
I hope it cooks faster.
-It's already cooked.
-Oh, no.
-Twenty seconds.
-Okay.
-It's okay. The filling is cooked.
-Right away.
-Fifteen seconds.
-Ten seconds.
-No salt?
-Not necessary.
-Eight.
PLATING THE CORN RIBS
JONG-WON GRABS THE STEAMER
Nine.
-My gosh.
-Eight. Seven.
PLATING THE CORN BEOMURI TOO
-Four. Three.
-Two. One.
-Take the dumpling out.
-Jong-won finishes first.
WHAT ABOUT YONG-WOOK?
HE ONLY NEEDS TO TAKE THE DUMPLING OUT
The wrapper's cooked.
-It just hasn't been browned.
-All the veggies inside are cooked.
-Director Yong-wook is done too.
-Goodness.
APPLAUSE
IN TATTERS…
-That was so much fun.
-It was.
Great job.
A BIG HUG
That cocktail looks so good. My gosh.
It's so pretty.
-Anyway, that was so cool.
-It was.
And now, both meals
were finished for Jung-hwa.
WOW♥
Okay, Land.
-It's so pretty.
-Jong-won finished first.
-South America, Europe, Korea, Yaho.
-Yaho.
SOUTH AMERICAN FLAVOR, WATERMELON CEVICHE
EUROPEAN FLAVOR, ZUCCHINI STEAK
KOREAN FLAVOR, SUPERSWEET CORN BEOMURI
CHEF SON JONG-WON'S
SOUTH AMERICA, EUROPE, KOREA, YAHO
Where should she begin?
First, on your way to South America,
you'll stop by a beautiful island.
-For an appetizer…
-Did he make something else?
…I prepared a beverage.
I'm sure no one saw me make it.
You're making this fun
by preparing many things.
-In the South Pacific, there is…
-The cup is pretty too.
a beautiful island called Fiji.
MINERAL WATER
JUST AS REFRESHING AS THAT ISLAND
-It's from that island.
-Geez.
SELF-CRINGING
He can even be funny now.
Not only is he a good chef,
he's a funny one too.
Fiji, yareu.
-Yareu.
-Sure.
Have some water first.
All right.
Then first, the ceviche?
Yes, the watermelon ceviche first.
-Watermelon ceviche?
-That sounds good.
-Isn't it usually made with fish?
-Yes.
You're right. It's a fish dish.
Does it come from Peru?
-Yes, Peru.
-Right?
-South America, yaho. Let me try it.
-South America, yaho.
First of all, it's so pretty,
so it makes me feel really great.
I'm already happy even before trying it.
-It's good to look at.
-Yes.
It looks like tuna.
Tuna or beef.
-Will she go, "South America, yaho"?
-Yaho.
YUM
It looks good.
A SMILE SPREADS
Okay?
Okay, Land?
Quiet.
-No talking.
-How scary.
It's so good.
It includes every flavor that I love,
and oddly,
it almost feels like it's made with fish.
It does?
It's just watermelon,
but it satisfies that taste.
It's really good.
Is it because of the cheese?
But there's no fish.
-It must be the shiso.
-I think so too.
I used lots of herbs that you had,
such as red shiso and mint,
and I used them with pepper.
So it's probably coming from
the mix of watermelon and pepper.
Watermelon and pepper can go together?
There's nothing short in this dish.
Yaho.
-Yaho.
-Peru, yaho.
ANOTHER BITE
It looks good.
MMM
IT LOOKS GOOD
-Is it that good?
-It's so good.
-So good.
-What a wonder.
It looks like
she might settle in South America.
-Let me enjoy it a little more.
-Okay.
-But the cruise is about to depart.
-We're about to set sail.
I knew it.
-It's off to a great start.
-I see.
Next up on your tour is Europe.
The cruise is departing.
He turned the zucchini into steak.
-Whoa.
-That's a zucchini steak.
What's at the bottom?
It's something I made
with tomatoes and other vegetables.
How did he do this in that short of time?
WILL SHE ALSO ENJOY THE EUROPEAN FLAVOR?
AN AUTOMATIC SMILE
Is the zucchini okay?
TOTALLY OKAY♥
OKAY, EUROPE♥
It's not overly done.
The zucchini itself is already delicious,
but he added Romanesco broccoli here
and gave it a crunchy texture,
finishing off with the tender cheese.
On top of that, the tomato sauce
makes up for the missing flavors,
so it's very delicious.
Lastly, Korea.
-Supersweet corn beomuri.
-Beomuri.
Ta-da.
How do I eat this?
I'll have to head there once again.
-Again?
There's a way to eat it.
I prepared this, hoping you'd
feel the touch of a grandmother
as you recover from your trip
to South America and Europe.
Scrape it like this.
-You're supposed to scrape it.
-Like that?
It's called beomuri
because you mix it as you eat it.
It's often made with mugwort.
-Yes, mugwort beomuri.
-Right.
Scrape it, put it down,
and sprinkle a bit of honey on it.
-It looks good.
-Supersweet corn beomuri.
-That looks good.
-Corn beomuri.
Try the beomuri alone first.
-And then with honey.
-I can smell it.
It really feels like
I returned home after a trip,
and I'm at my grandmother's house.
She's at her grandmother's place.
He powdered the rice himself
and made the beomuri.
CHOKING UP
Are you crying?
She met her grandma after a while.
SAVORING WITHOUT A WORD
Grandma.
CHOKING UP TOO
It's so good.
I also love tteok,
but I can't eat it often because of carbs.
But I'd eat this
when I return from a trip.
Try it with some honey.
Is that just regular honey?
She had truffle honey,
and truffle goes very well with corn.
He used all the right things.
My gosh.
Truffle honey and corn.
Look at this, Sooyoung.
-I want to try it so badly.
-Let me try it first.
OH, YOU'RE SUCH A TEASE
HOW WELL DO THEY GO TOGETHER?
It'll be exhilarating in your mouth.
-It must be sweet.
-Is it different with honey?
The truffle smell hits me hard.
It's very sweet and very delicious.
Like dipping garae-tteok, bar rice cake,
in grain syrup.
Even I can smell the truffle.
-Right?
-Yes.
SHOWING OFF
She's showing it off so much.
Gosh, it looks so good.
It really is.
Korea, yaho?
-Yaho!
-It's a yaho for Korea too.
Next, Brazil.
Let's visit Brazil now.
PASTEL FILLED
WITH HANGING TENDER AND VEGETABLES
SERVED WITH SMOKY SUPERSWEET CORN
AND SALSA TO ENHANCE THE PASTEL'S FLAVOR
BRAZILIAN COCKTAIL, CAIPIRINHA
DIRECTOR YOO YONG-WOOK'S BRAZIL, YAREU
I'm feeling anxious.
-Why?
This is just my taste.
-Because it's your taste.
-Yareu.
Everyone, get ready to party
until 3:00 a.m. tonight.
OH, WE'D "LOVE" THAT
She's getting started now.
I have work early tomorrow.
You still can't leave.
I ACTUALLY WOULD LOVE TO
-What's the first dish?
-In that tiny dish,
I prepared salsa, made with tomatoes,
cucumbers, red onion, and salsa verde.
Try the pastel with the sauce
and pick up the corn
to enjoy it like a rib.
-Okay.
-And have the Caipirinha as you like.
-Should I mix the sauce?
-Yes, please.
That sauce was really good.
Mix it all the way through.
-What's it like?
-It looks good.
It was good.
I really love tacos.
So it feels like that sauce.
That actually looks so good.
-I'll try it with lots of sauce.
-Okay.
-Have it with lots of sauce.
-Lots of sauce.
-It looks so good.
-My gosh.
-Hey, salsa.
-Brazilian flavor.
A BIG BITE
SMILING
Is it good? Do you like it?
Director Yong-wook, what is this?
It's so good.
-He was being a crybaby.
-What a crybaby.
-It's really good.
-It's really good!
My gosh.
-Yareu!
-Come on.
It's the death of yareu as a meme.
FAREWELL, YAREU…
Does the sauce play a big part?
Tacos can be bland without salsa, right?
-Yes.
-This sauce is so good.
-So you need it.
-Yes.
Also, he seemed unsure
when he deep-fried this,
-but it has that crunch to it.
-It does? I'm relieved.
At times, when the skin is too thick,
it feels too much when I eat it.
But it breaks apart with a crunch,
mixing nicely with the filling.
PERFECT FLAVOR AND TEXTURE
It's so good.
HAPPY
The cob is still attached,
so don't eat that.
That must be fantastic.
Hmm?
How did you grill this?
I didn't want to ruin
the corn's natural sweetness,
so I mixed it with olive oil,
meat seasoning, hot sauce,
and red pepper powder.
-Hot sauce.
It's really good.
When I go surfing in Bali,
there's a snack you can buy,
corn on the cob with seasoning.
It reminds me of that. It's so good.
It looks good.
I'm so excited for this cocktail.
Yes, that's something she would love.
It's like the water in her fridge.
-He made it with what's in the water.
-You're right.
What's it called again?
-Caipirinha.
Caipirinha.
-It actually means
-"…little country girl."
-It does?
WILL SHE LOVE THE FLAVOR TOO?
Caipirinha.
NODDING QUIETLY?
-She may not like it.
-It's a Brazilian cocktail, after all.
DOES SHE NOT LIKE IT?
It's really weird.
It doesn't taste like liquor.
It feels like he added
lots of lime into the water that I make.
I can't taste the alcohol.
That's why it's dangerous.
The first time
my Brazilian friend made that for me,
I kept drinking it
because I couldn't taste the alcohol,
and I was out after just one hour.
It's like that?
It sounds fascinating,
and now I can't wait to get tipsy.
-You can't wait?
-Right.
He said it can make you drunk.
No one is going home.
EMERGENCY FOR HIM
LET'S HURRY BEFORE SHE GETS DRUNK…
-But it was really good.
-I see.
It seems like she wants to be a bit tipsy.
-No, I was joking.
-All right.
I can't drink much.
ABOUT THIS MUCH?
Now, she'll decide right away.
-Please decide.
-What do I do?
Press one to choose Jong-won
and two to choose Yong-wook.
Please make your decision
and press the button.
PRESS
-I pressed one.
-She pressed one.
Where will the cruise ship dock?
Let's find out the result.
This round was titled, "Okay, Land."
Will it be Yoo Yong-wook's second win?
Or will it be Jong-won,
the current first place?
Who did Jung-hwa choose?
Who did she choose?
-All right.
-Who got the okay?
Will Yong-wook catch the big fish?
YOO YONG-WOOK WINS
DIRECTOR YOO YONG-WOOK'S
BRAZIL, YAREU WINS
-Are you serious?
-Thank you.
I can't believe this!
THIS IS HUGE
EMERGENCY
He takes Jong-won down.
-He defeated him.
-You won against first place.
I didn't want to leave this place.
She got off and loved it.
Chef Jong-won's dishes
were flawlessly beautiful and delicious.
But I had to travel to many places,
so I decided to anchor here
-and drink this until 3:00 a.m.
-It was the drink.
-The Caipirinha played a big part.
-Until 3:00 a.m.
I got to do this,
thanks to many people's help.
I didn't think I'd win,
so I didn't think of what to say.
He looks happier now than at CCW2.
Thank you for enjoying my dish.
CONGRATULATIONS
It's his second win.
He fought twice and won twice,
a win rate of 100%.
JONG-WON'S THE BEST
YONG-WOOK'S THE BEST
-Congratulations!
Thank you.
CONGRATS
Let's take ten.
AFTER THE FIRST ROUND
-Let me try that.
-That was fun.
It was really good.
GOING AFTER THE SUPERSWEET CORN BEOMURI
-Beomuri's good.
-Whoa.
IT'S SO GOOD
This is insane.
DIPPING IN THE HONEY
CHUCKLING
-Do you have water for ramyeon?
-Everything's good.
ALL SAYING WHATEVER THEY WANT TO
SOOYOUNG AND THE TUBBY TWINS
ENJOYED THE REST
Let's play the second cook-off
with Jung-hwa's ingredients.
Today, they are legitimate partners,
Chef Sam Kim and Chef Jung Ho-young.
The orthodox and the unorthodox
are now on the same boat,
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong
and Chef Lee Moon-jung.
Poong has played
a team round with Hyun-suk…
-Yes.
-…but it's your first with Moon-jung.
-Do you feel more at ease now?
Chef Hyun-suk
also isn't half bad, right?
THE CHEF OF 30 YEARS ISN'T HALF BAD
-He has a few tricks.
-Yes.
"A few tricks"?
Thank you, Chef Poong.
-I know that he tries hard.
-So jealous. I want his approval too.
Actually, Chef Moon-jung
is a certified master chef.
-A master chef.
-Yes, she is.
A certified master chef means
-that she's pretty much a technician.
-Yes.
I've never felt
more at ease to play as a team.
We were saying Poong
and Moon-jung make a good team,
but the same goes
for Sam and Ho-young as well.
They're guaranteed to have good teamwork.
This is our second time
actually cooking as a team,
but we were pretty much always a team.
Yes, I've seen you two work together.
Can you melt this?
ALWAYS HELPING WITHOUT COMPLAINING,
SAM KIM, THE KITCHEN TOOLMAN
So I feel confident today.
I knew it.
TEAM HO-YOUNG & SAM:
LOW-SUGAR BREAD, SLICED CHEESE, BRIE
SQUID, SHRIMP, SCALLOP, CHUCK FLAP TAIL,
ANCHOVY AEKJEOT, HOT SAUCE, AND MORE
What are they making?
We'll make something so delicious
that you wouldn't even notice
-that it's low-carb, low-sugar.
-I thought, "Why the bowls?"
For the first dish,
you said you couldn't eat noodles often
even though you liked them,
and you had thin glass noodles.
So we'll make
a spicy, sour, and sweet dish
just like yum woon sen in Thai cuisine.
-That sounds good.
-So we'll give it that strong flavor.
Sam will take the next dish.
It's called Philly cheese steak.
-Philly cheese steak.
-It's a sandwich
with meat and cheese inside.
It's considered pretty heavy,
but I'll serve it with râpées
made with zucchinis and carrots.
So that'll add
some healthiness to the dish.
Since you can't usually eat fast food,
we'll make something you can eat
without worrying too much.
-Who's going first? Ho-young?
-I'll go first.
-And then Sam.
-Then Sam.
My goal is to tag him in
at around six minutes.
He has a big role to play,
so if we lose, it's his fault.
"But if it goes well, kudos to me."
TEAM POONG & MOON-JUNG:
DOENJANG, SOYMILK NOODLES, RED ONION
BUTTON MUSHROOM, CUCUMBER,
CARROT, CABBAGE, TOMATO, AND MORE
Poong and Moon-jung, you're up too.
What are you making?
-The name of our dish is…
-There it is.
-They'll do something.
-They'll do it.
-Chinese Poison.
-Poison.
Chinese Poison.
So what are you making?
We caught on to something
you mentioned earlier.
"Jjajangmyeon."
You said you were craving it.
Jjajangmyeon?
We'll make low-carb,
low-sugar jjajangmyeon for you.
Can you do that?
Isn't it high-carb, high-sugar?
To suit the theme of low-carb, low-sugar,
we'll use your mother's homemade doenjang.
JJAJANGMYEON WITH DOENJANG?
-Doenjang jjajangmyeon is great.
-It is.
We'll make the sauce
with homemade doenjang.
-That's such a wonder.
-And one more.
-Menbosha.
-Menbosha?
-My gosh.
-She's in trouble.
-I'll make menbosha
with the sourdough bread you had.
I'll slice that thinly
and make it low-carb.
So who's up first?
-I'm up first.
-I knew it.
She's quick.
So Poong will finish?
-Yes.
-By any chance,
will Moon-jung use 14 minutes
and you, one minute?
What are you talking about?
It's 14 minutes and 50 seconds for her.
SEEMS LIKE HE REALLY WANTS TO DO THAT
Serve and ring the bell, that's his job.
All right, now.
Let us begin the team round.
Witch With a Wok
meets Cook of the Darkness.
The crazy Chinese siblings,
Kim Poong and Lee Moon-jung.
A chef and a kitchen toolman.
-"A kitchen toolman"?
The star-crazed brothers,
Ho-young and Sam are in this round.
It's our first two-on-two tag team round.
Who'll rise as the winners?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Let's do this!
HO-YOUNG STARTS!
MOON-JUNG STARTS!
POONG'S OUT, SAM'S OUT
Sam and Poong, sit back down.
She sharpens the knife quickly too.
Ho-young versus Moon-jung.
Okay.
That's good. Start right away.
-Is that the jjajang sauce?
-She's using doenjang.
It's her mother's homemade doenjang.
-Yes.
-She's frying homemade doenjang.
You can make jjajang sauce with doenjang.
It's really dark.
She's frying it like chunjang.
-It's Gangwon-do style.
-It's so dark.
-And it has a lot of umami.
-Yes.
-It's been fermented for a while.
-She's frying doenjang like it's chunjang.
-The same way.
That's cool.
-It's hard to imagine.
-Will it turn out like jjajang sauce?
Korean-style jjajang sauce
is made with Korean chunjang.
But the original Chinese jjajang sauce
is similar to doenjang, like that one.
-I see.
-Is that the case?
That's such a professional move
that Poong could never display.
That's why she's a master chef.
Wow.
HO-YOUNG FIGHTS BACK
-Cheese.
-For the Philly cheese steak?
-The Philly cheese steak.
-Cheese steak.
They'll use carrots too.
-Jung-hwa loves all those.
-I do.
-Carrots, what she eats every day.
-Yes.
STARTING ON THE YUM WOON SEN
SQUID
PERFECTLY CUT SQUID!
RAW SHRIMP MEAT
-Ho-young is…
-He just scored the squid.
He's using supersweet corn.
2. BLANCH SQUID, SHRIMP, AND CORN
MOON-JUNG STARTS ON THE MENBOSHA
Shrimp.
The menbosha.
Starch, salt, ground pepper.
All right. Okay.
Egg whites. What about those?
EGG WHITES
Is it okay for him to coach his partner?
Who cares? I'm just talking.
-It's okay.
-You can talk.
-You have to stir this.
-You're a team.
-You just can't help in person.
-Grind it hard.
MENBOSHA FILLING IS DONE!
He's peeling the zucchini.
-Rotating and peeling.
-Peeling something like that
is something Western chefs
have nothing on Japanese chefs.
Yes, Japanese chefs are so good at that.
-I see.
-That's really tough to do.
-At once.
-It's not easy.
And it's thin too.
He's good at peeling stuff.
You'll find that Ho-young
is always trying to peel me apart.
OH…
Sorry.
You laughed at everything Jong-won said.
Why the discrimination?
YOU'RE SO FUNNY, HYUN-SUK
Are you using the peel?
Yes, the peel has
a nice, sweet flavor to it,
so I'm using just this part.
You're fast. Excellent.
MOON-JUNG OVERPOWERS HIM WITH HER SPEED
Nice speed!
RED ONION
THE CLASS OF THE MASTER CHEF!
She's so cool.
DELICACY VS. POWER
Three minutes have gone by.
-It's okay.
-We have enough time.
It's okay. We got this.
We got this.
JAPANESE CUISINE IS ALL ABOUT CUTTING!
Good.
He also isn't any less skilled
when it comes to cutting. Look.
He chops the zucchini peel.
My gosh.
-That's so pretty.
-He's so delicate.
I love the way Japanese chefs cut.
His fingers may look blunt,
but his chopping skills are delicate.
"His fingers may look blunt"?
CHEF & MY FRIDGE IS SPICY
3. SALT CHOPPED ZUCCHINI AND CARROT
Ho-young and Sam are making
two different dishes,
so it'd be better
if Ho-young finished as early as he can.
-You're right.
-That is so, right?
INTO THE SEAFOOD WATER!
What's that? Glass noodles?
-Thin glass noodles.
-I think
he's making yum woon sen now.
MOON-JUNG WANTS TO FINISH PREPPING
FOR POONG'S SAKE
CUCUMBER
CARROT
We'll add your favorite, carrots.
-Into the jjajang sauce?
-Yes.
-Can you do that?
-Because she likes them.
Also, the ingredients
for jjajangmyeon are usually diced,
but we're julienning everything.
-I see that.
-You can eat them with your noodles.
-Because she likes veggies.
-So she julienned them?
Green onion.
Big pieces of green onion. Good.
That Chinese kitchen knife is powerful.
THE GREEN ONION OIL!
-She's really fast.
-She makes it look so easy.
CHUCK FLAP TAIL & HANGING TENDER
Meat.
-She chops the meat quickly too.
-She's so fast.
And it looks so good.
3. CHOP AND COOK CHUCK FLAP TAIL
AND HANGING TENDER IN GREEN ONION OIL
Ten minutes left.
We decided to add tomatoes
to our jjajangmyeon.
-Really?
-It'll taste good.
-Have you ever had tomato jjajangmyeon?
-No.
-It's really good.
-Not even doenjang jjajangmyeon.
Moon-jung versus Ho-young.
A tag team round.
You'd better leave as much time
as you can leave for the next person.
He should leave at about seven and a half,
since he said he'd use six minutes.
-His six minutes are already up.
-Yes, it's over already.
CHOPPING CALMLY!
ANCHOVY AEKJEOT
GARLIC
What's that? Hot sauce?
He added anchovy aekjeot,
hot sauce, and garlic.
-The yum woon sen sauce.
-Is that hot sauce?
ALLULOSE
LOW-SUGAR OYSTER SAUCE55
WATER
LIME JUICE
-That looks good.
-Sam.
-Yes.
-Is it going well?
-Yes. He should speed up though.
-Is everything good? No? Speed up?
Are you adding tomatoes in there?
Tomatoes? Yes.
That's small enough.
It'll break down in the pan anyway.
COOK WITH MEAT!
Excellent! That's it!
THIS TIME, IT'S SMOKY!
That's it! Yes.
You're doing so great.
They're flustered.
WHO'S FLUSTERED?
-It's okay.
-Add them all. Everything!
-Everything in!
-It's nice and quiet
when Poong is cooking in the kitchen,
-but when he's not, he's so loud.
-He's doing it.
What an eyesore.
Moon-jung needs to do
as much as she can for Poong's sake.
Yes, I love it. She's so fast.
-Excellent. We have no time.
-Good job.
BRISKET
DROP!
5. ADD VEGGIES, FRIED DOENJANG,
BRISKET, FLAVORED SOY SAUCE, OYSTER SAUCE
Passing eight minutes.
What about the noodles?
They haven't sliced the bread either.
You don't have much time.
Will she really use 14 minutes?
-Excellent job.
-Eight minutes.
CHINESE FOOD IS ALL ABOUT SMOKINESS!
-Seven minutes have gone by.
-That looks awesome.
It smells like a Chinese restaurant.
It smells smoky.
WITCH WITH A WOK IN THE FIERY PIT!
-Okay. Allulose!
-Allulose.
ALLULOSE WILL ADD THE SWEETNESS!
This is so cool.
By their looks,
it feels like Ho-young would do that.
But he's cooking very calmly.
-What's that?
-I can smell the jjajang sauce from here.
You're halfway done.
Seven and a half minutes.
He has used more than half the time.
He used up a lot.
Sam won't have enough time.
-So just mix and serve? That's it?
-Yes.
You just have to check
if it needs more sweetness.
I'm done.
SAM KIM IS UP!
Now, Sam's up.
Sam's in, Ho-young's out.
They've switched.
Sam has to finish up.
Why won't your team switch?
Excellent.
He's just the cheerleader.
Where's the butter?
8. SPREAD BUTTER
ON LOW-CARB BREAD AND TOAST
Yes, that's it.
-The meat.
-Yes, the meat.
9. GRIND CHUCK FLAP TAIL IN A BLENDER
-Sam went in without much time left.
-I'm short of time.
I don't have much time.
Can he cook the meat in time?
BUTTON MUSHROOM, ONION
10. COOK BUTTON MUSHROOM,
ONION, AND CHUCK FLAP TAIL
Now, slice the bread for the toast.
HOW ARE YOU THIS BRAZEN?
-Moon-jung is doing everything.
-Yes, excellent job.
POONG SHOWS SUPPORT FROM THE SIDE!
SHRIMP, SCALLOPS
IN THE END, MOON-JUNG PREPPED
ALL THE INGREDIENTS ALONE
THIS IS WHY HE CHOSE MOON-JUNG!
Mix them. Yes.
Poong's cooking with his mouth.
You're cheating.
How is this cheating?
Can you call this a team round?
This is a team round. We're a team.
Six minutes remain,
but Poong hasn't stepped in yet.
-We're a team.
-Our production crew should say something.
-Six minutes.
-The toast is that big?
-She's making the toast too.
-Good job!
-That looks so good.
-Excellent job.
-Menbosha.
-The menbosha looks great.
When will Poong step in?
-Put this on top?
-Yes, on top.
-Isn't it too thick?
-No, it's not.
It's not. I'll do the rest.
-Will that cook in time?
-It will.
-Are you done? Yes? Go!
-I'm done.
-Go!
-Poong's going in now!
He's going in.
-Touch.
-Moon-jung, step out.
-Poong went in at five minutes.
-Okay.
-Five minutes left.
-Five minutes.
Please report from the kitchen, Jung-hwan.
Yes, the two-on-two tag team round.
-Is the yum woon sen finished?
-Yes.
It is.
Look at that.
-Wait a second.
-It's as big as a brick.
-Not that one. The heat is too low.
-Isn't the oil…
-…too cold?
-No.
He's just like me in the previous round.
It has to be cooked in low heat.
-The temperature has to be low.
-Over low heat.
It's on low heat.
SAM MAKES PHILLY CHEESE STEAK
-Salt.
-What?
EGG
WHAT SAUCE IS HE MAKING WITH EGG YOLK?
11. MIX EGG YOLK, BARBECUE SAUCE,
AND OLIVE OIL TO MAKE BARBECUE MAYO
-It's a mess.
-The oil won't spread.
He's now making chili oil.
She just added starch water.
Poong is practically doing nothing.
-Three minutes and thirty seconds!
-Okay.
-I don't have much time.
-It's okay.
Do that first and try it.
The roux.
12. COOK FLOUR IN BUTTER TO MAKE ROUX
AND POUR MILK TO MAKE BÉCHAMEL
ADDING MELTED CHEESE IN MILK!
He's toasting bread here.
-What's this sauce?
-Cheese sauce.
Team tag round isn't easy.
Mustard.
CARROT & ZUCCHINI RÂPÉES
Sugar is over there.
Where?
14. MIX ZUCCHINI & CARROTS WITH OLIVE OIL,
WHOLE GRAIN MUSTARD, PEPPER, LEMON JUICE
It's going into the hot oil!
Just like that?
At first, he cooked it over low heat
only to cook it once again over high heat.
-That looks good. Good job.
-Okay. Now, the sauce.
-Three minutes. You two, hands off.
-We're done.
-The meat.
-Ho-young, hands off.
Moon-jung, hands off.
Those two are the only ones cooking.
No, not yet.
-What's she doing?
-Hands off!
DROPPING THE SOYMILK NOODLES!
-She's cheating.
-Hands off.
LIKE BROTHER, LIKE SISTER
-Look at that.
-It's jjajangmyeon.
ADDING A JUNKY FACE
Jung-hwan, try the jjajang sauce.
Let's see if it tastes like jjajangmyeon.
Does it taste like jjajang sauce?
Or is it only making you judge them?
What's it like?
Did he just cough up blood?
Is it jjajang or judgy?
It's somewhere in between.
It doesn't taste like jjajang.
-What?
-Nothing like jjajang?
-It tastes like gang-doenjang.
-It tastes like doenjang.
Poong must've ruined it.
DROPPING ALLULOSE!
No, don't! Stop!
It's over. It's done.
-Allulose!
-It's over.
WE WON…
-But that doenjang is delicious.
-It's okay.
It's probably too sweet.
-Serve the râpées on the side.
-Where?
ALMOND SPREAD
COOKED CHUCK FLAP TAIL
Sam begins to plate the dish.
He's plating his dish calmly.
-Cheese on top. Jung-hwan!
-Yes?
-There's leftover meat, right?
-Yes.
-There's more meat.
-Is he making it runny on purpose?
The meat.
Let me try this.
One minute and ten seconds left.
Do you think she'll be able to know?
Or will she sing, "Don't Know"?
She will be able to know.
Is it good?
-It's great.
-It must be good.
I think the meat needs a bit more salt.
Does it taste bland?
Oh, but there's cheese, so it's okay.
The meat itself was bland.
One minute left.
Chili oil.
CHILI OIL EXPERT, KIM POONG!
Even chili oil?
Okay. One second.
-You're adding chili oil too?
-All right.
-Make the sauce.
-Okay.
Turn off the heat
to keep the noodles firm.
It's fine. These noodles don't get soggy.
SLURP
GOOD!
Lemon juice.
It's over there. There's the lemon.
-What else?
-That's it.
The toast. I have to get the toast.
The menbosha is slowly burning.
Is the toast burning?
TAKE IT OUT!
-Take it out now!
-Take it out!
MUST TAKE IT OUT!
-It must be hot!
-He's shaking!
TAKE IT OUT!
-Wait a second.
-He has trouble getting it out.
-It looks burnt!
-Oh, no.
It's not.
-It looks good.
-It's perfect.
It's burnt!
Flip it over. It's burnt!
Flip it over!
-It's burnt!
-Flip it over.
It's so tough to choose one.
ONLY HAS TO FINISH THE YUM WOON SEN
Where is it? In here?
In the right fridge. The lower part.
Down there. The left door.
SERVE YUM WOON SEN, AND IT'S DONE!
-And shiso.
-Twenty seconds!
Twenty seconds!
Yum woon sen is done.
Ho-young's dish is finished.
Hurry up, Sam.
-Serve the jjajangmyeon.
-Do we cut this or not?
-Just put it down. Right here.
-Ten. Nine.
GIGGLING
THE SOURDOUGH MENBOSHA IS READY
-Five. Four.
-Cucumber!
-The cucumber!
-Ring the bell.
-One! Time's up.
-Ring it.
SAM AND HO-YOUNG FINISH FIRST!
CAN ONLY SERVE WHAT HE HAS IN HIS HANDS
-That's way too much.
-Is that family-sized?
It's family-sized.
4 SERVINGS OF JJAJANGMYEON…
You're right. It's family-sized.
Poong is done too.
ABUNDANT
So that's what happens
when Poong finishes up.
It's the first time
we're seeing him overplate.
ABOUT TO OVERFLOW
It's overflowing.
THE JUNKY LOW-CARB, LOW-SUGAR DISHES
ARE ON THEIR WAY
Are these really low-carb, low-sugar?
-That looks good.
-Right?
-The menbosha looks good.
-It smells great.
It's so difficult to choose one.
And now, everything
has been prepared for Jung-hwa.
THANK YOU
-It's a hefty amount.
-It is.
The quantity really is junky.
-Too much to the point that it's junky?
-Yes.
Team Ho-young and Sam finished first.
LOW-CARB, LOW-SUGAR, DON'T KNOW
A MEATY AND CHEESY SANDWICH
AND RÂPÉES TO LESSEN THE GUILT
AND YUM WOON SEN SALAD
SAM KIM & JUNG HO-YOUNG'S LOW-CARB,
LOW-SUGAR? DON'T KNOW, CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT
Try the sandwich first.
Eat it with the sauce on the dish.
It has to have that junk food flavor.
-Put lots of sauce on it.
-Dip the sandwich.
Lots of sauce on top.
-It's full of filling.
-Meat and all.
Let me show you.
JUNKY CROSS SECTION
It looks so good.
SIGH…
-Okay. Lots of sauce.
-Lots of sauce.
Gosh, that looks so good.
The cheese has all melted, Sooyoung.
The cheese has melted!
Sooyoung, don't you want some too?
I really want some.
HERE WE GO
I hope it's as junky as it could get.
Oh, boy.
I hope she likes it.
NERVOUS
It's so good.
-It's really good.
-She says it's good.
There are times when you crave
something this creamy and rich.
It's perfect for those cravings.
But this bread is low-carb,
so I can eat it guilt-free.
This cheese sauce is so rich,
and it's really good.
Is the sauce low-sugar too?
Yes, everything is low-sugar.
-We used the blue eggs too.
-The blue eggs.
-And made mayo with it.
-There's an egg in this?
-Yes, the blue egg.
-When did they throw it in?
When you start to feel a bit guilty,
you can have a bite
of the zucchini and carrot râpées.
-"Feel guilty"?
-Like a side dish.
Aren't these veggies so pretty?
TOP WITH PRETTY VEGGIES
YUM
SYNCHRONIZED
Mmm.
-It's her day today.
-She's usually under self-discipline.
She usually doesn't eat like this.
A THUMBS-UP
THANK YOU
These veggies are so good.
What's that like?
Zucchinis and carrots.
The crunchy texture adds a nice touch
to the heavy sandwich,
so it makes it more refreshing.
I can enjoy both rich
and refreshing flavors at the same time.
It tastes like
I'd put on a kilogram right now.
It has a junky taste,
but it actually isn't.
-Because the ingredients are healthy.
-Yes.
That was satisfying.
-Yum woon sen.
I wonder if she'll like this.
I topped it with shiso to add some aroma.
Mix it well and eat it with the seafood.
Okay.
-That won't make you gain weight at all.
-Low-carb noodles.
You're right. It won't.
She eats those
when she craves jjajangmyeon.
But it will, if you eat tons of it.
It smells so good.
-It's as if I'm at a Thai restaurant.
-Thai restaurant.
Ho-young made that calmly
while Moon-jung tossed the wok.
-That's why it's yum woon sen.
-Sure.
-He calmly made it yummy.
-Made it yummy.
The yum woon sen he made calmly.
Let me have a bite.
YUM
A THUMBS-UP AFTER THE FIRST BITE
They're exchanging eyes.
She gives a thumbs-up.
What's it like?
It's the most delicious
yum woon sen I've had.
I can't believe this.
A ROUND OF APPLAUSE
It's the best yum woon sen
she has ever had.
That's huge.
When I had it in Thailand,
the fish sauce hit me a little too hard.
But this is made perfectly to my taste.
-It must be seasoned well.
-And I don't think
this will put any weight on me,
no matter how much I eat it.
-Because it won't, right?
-Right.
It's so good.
-It's the best yum woon sen.
-I see.
She looks pleased.
SAM & HO-YOUNG'S DISH WAS PERFECT
That was Sam and Ho-young.
The problem is the next one,
this jjajangmyeon.
A HUGE PORTION OF JJAJANGMYEON
SOURDOUGH MENBOSHA WITH SPECIAL SAUCE
KIM POONG & LEE MOON-JUNG'S CHINESE POISON
Most dishes leave
about 30% to 40% of blank space.
-But this is…
-It's full.
No blank space.
I thought it was important
for the dish to look like junk food too.
It was intentional.
Sure. This one looks like a bath sponge.
IT DOES LOOK SIMILAR…
Thank you.
GASP!
It really looks junky.
-It already looks junky, right?
-Is this oil?
IS THIS ALL OIL?
Is it olive oil, though?
Olive oil?
-That cooking oil is open.
-It's cooking oil.
It's made with 100% soybeans.
-Vegetable oil.
-I made chili oil with 100% vegetable oil.
I made it with hot peppers
the farmers grew.
Oh, sure.
Most people enjoy
the usual olive oil, don't they?
That's why we used
this cooking oil made with soybeans.
WHAT NOW?
TIMEOUT
-You don't have to try.
-It's irrelevant.
That's a warning.
You must feel anxious.
What are the noodles?
-I used the soybean noodles you had.
-I see.
So there's zero carbs in those noodles.
-It's just soybeans.
-Soybean noodles.
The point is, is it like jjajangmyeon?
Can it act as a replacement?
It looks like
it'll give you a blood sugar spike.
I've never seen anything like this before.
It's too much, right?
-Yes, it looks like junk food.
-It's junky.
-It's too junky.
-She probably had never eaten like this.
-I'm dying to find out.
-She's curious.
Will it taste like jjajangmyeon?
FINALLY TAKES A BITE
It's made with your mother's doenjang.
-Yes?
-Her eyes widened.
-So yes?
-Does it taste like jjajangmyeon?
-It does?
-Yes.
RELIEVED
-But she used only doenjang.
-Yes.
It tastes a bit like jjajangmyeon.
It does?
Or am I tricking myself?
Am I thinking,
"This is jjajangmyeon, and it has to be"?
-Well, but…
-But it's good.
I'm curious.
-Did you add lots of sugar?
-No.
-Her allulose.
-Allulose.
-How does it taste like jjajangmyeon?
-It's a wonder.
-It tastes like it.
-It does.
Chunjang is a paste
made by fermenting soybeans and flour.
After that,
caramel coloring agent is added
to turn it into that black paste
we're all very familiar with.
-But we just skipped on the coloring bit.
-Yes.
Then we fried doenjang the same way,
so it'll taste like jjajangmyeon.
It's much healthier.
There's no caramel coloring agent.
This is fascinating.
How did Poong contribute to the noodles?
I added the junky chili oil.
And I suggested that we add tomatoes.
It goes quite well with it.
Can you taste the tomatoes?
I can't exactly taste it,
but its sweet and sourness
balance out the saltiness of doenjang.
YOU'RE RIGHT
-It's really good.
-I see.
-Next, the bath sponge thing.
-Bath sponge?
-There's a bath sponge shaped like that.
-I know.
It's menbosha.
Should she dip it in chili oil?
That's the sauce I made
with a dash of chili oil.
I mixed it with your barbecue sauce
and tomato paste for sourness.
Gosh, that sound.
CURIOUS
Do you want to hear it again?
CHEF & MY FRIDGE SINCE 2014
75,858 VIEWS
THE ASMR OF AN AVID MUKBANG VIEWER
ASMR.
It really is junk food.
There's oil seeping out.
OIL SEEPS OUT…
It's probably shrimp juice.
-Shrimp juice?
GASLIGHTING INTO THINKING IT'S SHRIMP…
Isn't that too greasy?
I got rid of the oil mostly.
I can't tell who'll win.
It's now dripping on the floor.
-Right?
-It's shrimp juice.
Is this really low-carb, low-sugar?
CRUNCH
-It's high-fat for sure.
-High-fat.
-It looks so good.
-That has to be good.
-She just let out a sigh.
-That was a sigh.
-Is that positive or negative?
-Right?
-Was it that good?
-Or is it…
First of all, it's unbelievably good.
But it's also a total junk food.
Do you feel guilty?
-I do feel guilty.
-I see.
-She feels guilty for eating it.
-But this is
made with sourdough and shrimp.
-So it's fine, right?
-It is.
But compared to your usual diet,
you feel like you're committing a crime.
That's not the case.
That is the case.
-You are not guilty.
-Say it louder.
-That is the case.
-Sam has something to say.
I thought she'd feel guilty.
No way. There's no need for that.
It was delicious.
Why don't we all try it?
-Try some, Sooyoung.
-Thank you.
What is this?
This is my seat, right?
HAPPY
You might take your uniform off to eat.
I should really just
come as a guest at this point.
-It's a feast.
-Wow.
-A feast.
-Yes.
-People will think we're the guests.
-This one first.
Please try it, Sooyoung.
Mmm!
-This is good.
-Isn't it?
-It's so good.
-This is good.
-It's really good.
-It is.
-How did he do this?
-Ho-young really is
good at everything.
It's also the best yum woon sen
I have ever had.
It's so good.
You didn't use fish sauce, right?
She didn't have it,
but she had anchovy aekjeot.
-So I made use of that.
-This is to die for.
I like how it's not overly done.
And the way all of this seafood
is cooked is perfect.
I want to drink this sauce.
NEXT, PHILLY CHEESE SANDWICH
YUM
It's unbelievable, right?
GLARING
-What's wrong?
-Philly cheese steak.
-It's good.
-Can you start selling these?
THANK YOU
-Right?
-It's a shame that only we get to eat.
It's so good with the sauce.
CHOMP
This is too good.
ISN'T IT?
Next, Poong and Moon-jung's dish.
-I was curious.
-Chinese Poison.
This one looks pretty good too.
Jjajangmyeon and menbosha.
-It tastes like jjajangmyeon.
-It does.
It's jjajangmyeon.
-It's just jjajangmyeon.
-It's jjajangmyeon. It's so good.
If I didn't see them cooking,
I wouldn't have known the difference.
It's so good.
It's really good.
DONE WITH THIS
MOVING ON TO THE LEFTOVER SAUCE
HMM?
-Rice…
-Do you need rice?
Rice, please.
This is hard.
Is this only possible
with homemade doenjang?
You can do it with store-bought ones,
but when you do that,
it's better to add a bit of flour to it.
It has that charred flavor.
-Smoky flavor.
-Smoky.
Maillard reaction.
-I tasted that smoky flavor.
-Smoky flavor.
I've often had jjajang sauce
made with doenjang.
And among those dishes,
this was the most similar
to actual jjajang sauce.
And when you have
really good jjajangmyeon,
-you need that grease coating your lips.
-Yes.
-That coat.
-And soon after a bite,
it was nice to feel
that coat of grease on my lips.
It tasted like
a delicious bowl of jjajangmyeon.
Did you enjoy your elaborate meal?
She looks full.
My dress feels too tight now.
She had a lot.
-I still have the menbosha.
-The menbosha.
She'll have to choose soon.
The texture of the sourdough menbosha
is great.
-It's much better than regular bread.
-Much better, right?
Yes, this is really good.
MMM!
It's so hard to choose.
-It is. It's really hard.
-What do I do now?
Press one for Sam and Ho-young,
and two for Poong and Moon-jung.
Jung-hwa's choice.
Press the button.
My finger is going like this.
What do I do?
-Is it hard?
-It's hard.
I'll pick one.
Pick one.
Okay?
-Okay.
She pressed one now.
Which team did she choose?
Let's find out.
Show us.
That was "Junky Low-Carb, Low-Sugar,"
played as a relay round, a tag team round.
Will it be Poong and Moon-jung?
-Or Ho-young and Sam?
-And Sam?
Will Ho-young and Sam
-get their revenge on Poong?
-Please.
Or will Poong and Moon-jung
win another star?
Who won?
Who did she choose?
Who is it?
KIM POONG AND LEE MOON-JUNG WIN
KIM POONG AND LEE MOON-JUNG'S
CHINESE POISON WINS
Poong and Moon-jung.
EXCITED
That jjajangmyeon was tough to beat.
It was so hard.
Choosing was very hard for both rounds.
-This is way too good.
-It's still hard.
I put the focus
on which ones felt more junky.
Yes, it's so junky.
Also, it was meaningful to me
that my mom's doenjang
can turn into jjajangmyeon.
I always crave it so much
when I'm on a diet,
so it was great to know
I can make it low-carb, low-sugar.
It was really touching.
That was my reasoning.
THANK YOU
Now, with Moon-jung next to you,
how do you feel, Poong?
When Hyun-suk and I played as a team,
we had won together,
and we won again today.
I might be the victory fairy.
-Just a thought.
-The victory fairy.
How brazen of you.
It all goes to Moon-jung.
She gave them a really good fight.
Please put the stars
on Poong and Moon-jung.
Great job.
That was Poong's ninth win,
and Moon-jung's fourth win.
-Already?
-Congratulations!
-Thank you.
-They win the team round.
-Congratulations.
-Look at him.
COMING UP: THE PREVIEW
Is it your birthday?
Wait, are you 010…
The love story starts there.
By any chance, do you like Chapaguri?
-Strip loin.
-With strip loin?
Cut!
TWO VETERAN ACTORS
CHO YEO-JEONG & HA SEOK-JIN
This is the 30th year since her debut.
What's the secret
behind your youthfulness?
I hold back, reluctantly.
I eat jjajangmyeon and ramyeon
probably twice a year.
SHOCKED
I can't live like that.
-Are you looking for healthy--
-No!
THE MOST URGENT SHOUT
I want to eat a lot
even if it's loaded with calories.
A ROUND FOR CHO YEO-JEONG,
DISHES LOADED WITH CALORIES
RAISE HER SUPPRESSED APPETITE
DON'T HOLD BACK ON HER FAVORITES
WOW
IT'S SO EXCITING
MERCILESS AMOUNT OF OIL
NO LIMIT ON CALORIES
EXPLODING WITH EXCITEMENT
-My gosh.
-That cheese.
GOING COMPLETELY RECKLESS
WHICH DISH BROKE
HER 30 YEARS OF DISCIPLINE?
She loves it so much.
Isn't it good?
It's so good.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn